prfire.co.uk 2009-03-01

# Privacy Statement

**Prfire** knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting **Prfire** you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

**What Personal Information About Customers Does** **Prfire** **Gather?**  
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve our press releases. At **Prfire** Here are the types of information we gather.

**Information You Give Us:**  
We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing press releases and communicating with you.

**Automatic Information:**  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses **Prfire** Scroll to the bottom of this page to see examples of the information we receive. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at **Prfire** if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.

**E-mail Communications:**  
To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from **Prfire** if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please tell us so.

**What About Cookies?**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as automatic login and permanent shopping carts for storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.  
The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of **Prfire's** features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

**Does** **Prfire** **Share the Information It Receives?**  
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only with the subsidiaries **Prfire** controls and as described below.  
**Promotional Offers:**  
Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of **Prfire** customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address.

**Protection of Open Realty Templates and Others:**  
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of **Prfire** , our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**With Your Consent:**  
Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**  
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using [PayPal ](https://www.paypal.com/)as one of our payment processors, they process the credit cards, so **Prfire** will NEVER see you credit card number. Paypal protects your privacy and information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.  
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**  
If you choose to visit **Prfire** , your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of The United Kingdom If you have any concern about privacy at **Prfire** , please send us a thorough description to and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice  will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to **Prfire** , but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.

**Automatic Information**  
Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; and products you viewed or searched for.
